Neetesh Kumar Agarwal (1) Featured



Software Developer seeking roles in Software Engineering, Software Development, Application Support, Project Management, Change Management, Defect Management, Quality Management, Requirement Gathering, JavaScript, Bootstrap, ASP. Net, Python, JIRA, HTML, CSS, Git



Current Designation: Software Developer Total Experience: 9 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Wtvision Solutions Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Location: Delhi Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Delhi / NCR, Pune, Lucknow

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Engineering, Software Development, Application Support, Project

Management, Change Management, Defect Management, Quality Management, Requirement Gathering, JavaScript, Bootstrap, ASP. Net, ADO. Net, Python, Django, JIRA, HTML, CSS, Git

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

8+ years of experience in all phases of software development life cycle (SDLC) especially in Design, Development, Deploying of applications, and implementing Client/Server applications using Microsoft technologies - .NET Framework, SQL Server and Python-Django

To work continuously for the betterment of my skills in good professional organization to achieve leading position in project planning and development activities

Work Experience

Wtvision Solutions as Software Developer

Mar 2013 to Till Date

Projects # - News Website(Currently Working) - For Office : Technology Used - Python, Django, Boot Strap, Sql Lite

Projects # - 24*7 Web Based News Channel (Currently Working) - For Office :

Technology Used - Node, Web Api, Angular

Projects # - Elections Project - For DD News (All Assembly Election & General Election) MI Marathi(Mumbai) - Maharashtra Assembly Election - Lok Sabha TV Technology Used -SQL Server, Windows Application C#.Net and WPF, VizRt, Asp.net

Budget: - Rail Budget and Union Budget for DD NEWS Technology Used - MY SQL, Windows Application C#.Net, VizRt

Bombay Stock Exchange Show for DD NEWS (SQL SERVER, Iron Python and Vizrt)

Sports Project: - Cricket - Bangladesh Vs Sri Lanka 2014 (TEST, ODI, T20I) In Bangladesh, Pakistan Vs Zimbabwe 2015 (ODI, T20I), KARBONN PREMIURE LEAGUE,

PAKSITAN PREMIERUR LEAGUE. Champions Trophy 2017 for DD Sports (Touch Screen & Augmented Reality), Ranji Trophy(2018-19), Road Safety World Series(Maharashtra 2020)

Super Fight League, Studio Shows, Kabaddi, Shooting Projects, Volley Ball Project

Badminton - Premier Badminton League Season 1 & 2, Syed Modi Lucknow (2014 - 17)

Tennis Project - Aircel Open 2014 - 2019 (now Tata Open), CTL (Season 1 & 2)

Football Projects - I league, Super Cup, Internation Continental Cup, Touch Screen Projects, Goals for Glory for DD Sports(Touch Screen) and so on.

Pool & Snooker: Indian Open Snooker (2013- 2019) & Cue Slam 2017

Auctions Project :- HIL Auction, T10 Dubai Auction, Master Cricket Dubai,

Technology Used -SQL Server, C# WPF, Iron Python, VB Script in Vizrt,

Window Based Project: News Publisher and Ninja Lister (for online Marketing), Application for Office Work Use

Technology Used -SQL Server, XML and Windows Form C#.Net, MySQL

Web Projects: - Quiz Show for Spain, Web Sites for DOS Society - AIIMS DELHI, Article to video converter, Websites for ISCKRS - Society, Commentator System for Sports Project (Using Html, CSS, Java Script, Socket, Boot Strap), Ipad Solution to play augmented reality in Elections & Football Event.

Technology Used -SQL Server, Web Application C#.Net, ASP.Net, Payment Gateway (CCAvenue and Pilums) Integration, Node, Angular, Boot strap, Python and Django

Operational Experience: T20 World Cup Opening Ceremony Bangladesh (Studio Show), Football in Neo and BSE Show in DD NEWS. Election in MI Marathi.

PCR Live Support: Live Support for Cricket Series, Badminton, Election, Tennis, Auction Project, Football and Budget and many other projects.

Onsite Exp: - Football and Election Project in Lisbon, Portugal, International Cricket and Opening Ceremony in Bangladesh, Snooker in Ahmadabad, Athletics in Bhubaneswar, PBL in many locations and so on.

Soft Solutions Limited as Assistant Software Developer Dec 2010 to Jun 2012

Education

UG: B.Sc (Maths) from Chhatrapati Shahu Ji Maharaj University in 2006

PG: MCA (Computers) from Ajay Kumar Garg Engineering College in 2010

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
C# , Python, VB Script	
MS-SQL SERVER , MY-SQL,SQL LITE	
ASP.Net, ADO.Net, Django	
Java Script, HTML,CSS,Boot Strap	
Windows Form,Tkniter(python)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				

Hindi

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time